- [Narrator] The world is unpredictable,
这个世界是不可预测的，你永远不知道什么时候你的生活会崩溃
and you never know when your
life might come under threat.
威胁值得付出准备，但不是每个人都拥有内在的
It pays to be prepared.
生存本能可以打败您必须解决的十个谜题
But not everyone possesses
inbuilt survival instincts.
活着，让我们找出
Can you defeat these 10 riddles
水上十号头想象你被困在一个房间里，
that you must solve to stay alive?
它慢慢地充满了到处都检查过的水，没有办法
Let's find out.
关掉水或逃跑，你会感觉到水位上升
(gentle music)
每过一秒钟，不仅是水的寒冷使您
Number 10.
尖叫，但距离您只有五分钟的帮助知识
Head Above Water.
几分钟左右，直到整个房间都被水淹没为止
Imagine you're trapped in a room
呼吸三分钟，但是你确实有一根稻草，一根绳子，一个水桶和一个
and it's slowly filling with water.
他们中的人有能力为您节省时间并挽救您的生命
You've checked everywhere
and there's no way
很快，您只有十秒钟的时间来制定计划
to turn off the water,
or to make an escape.
现在也许您可以像浮潜一样使用吸管，但是一旦使用将无济于事
And you can feel the water level
水到达天花板时，绳索将在许多其他方面有用
rising with every passing second.
生死攸关的情况，但抱歉，现在对您不利，实际上
It's not only the coldness of
the water making you squeal,
可以为您提供额外时间的桶，直到帮助到达
but the knowledge that
help is five minutes away,
将其翻转过来放在您的头上，您将有一个气泡，
and you only have two minutes or so
将为您提供您所需的额外时间，直到帮助到达9号故障
until the entire room is flooded.
现在您决定跳伞跳伞以庆祝不溺水
There's no way you can hold
因为为什么当你从飞机上跳下来时，你会觉得自己真的在飞
your breath for three minutes.
尽管您的厄运还在继续，但您比以往任何时候都活着的时间更长，
You do, however, have a
straw, a rope, and a bucket.
您的降落伞无法打开，您正在从空中坠落，令人震惊
And one of them has the power to
速率，当您失控时，您会看到下面的硬地冲向
buy you time and save your life.
你要如何摆脱这种困境，你要卷曲成一个
Which item is it?
保护您的头部和内部器官免受撞击的球
Be quick.
相信备用降落伞，还是会尝试调动另一个
You only have 10 seconds
to come up with a plan.
跳伞运动员并紧紧抓住它们，你只有十秒钟，直到太快
(drum beats)
迟到要救自己
Now, maybe you could use
the straw like a snorkel,
您问题的答案很明显，只有备用降落伞是唯一的选择
but that won't be helpful once
保证拯救您的生命，ing缩成一团可能会减少
the water reaches the ceiling.
损坏，但也可能不会损坏，因为紧贴其他跳伞者
The rope would be useful in so many
他们杀死了第八死回生
other life-or-death situations, but sorry,
您要在户外大自然中漫步，这是一个美丽的晴天，
it's no good to you right now.
你在吹口哨，就在做白日梦
It's actually the bucket that will buy you
午餐一次回到营地，以至于您不会注意到
a little extra time until help arrives.
一头巨大的棕熊站在你面前几米处，一阵恐慌
Turn it upside-down,
put it over your head,
当熊看着你的眼睛并咆哮着你时，你会怎么做
and you'll have an air
bubble that will give you
如果您站稳脚跟并吓scar死亡，请逃避死亡的停顿
the extra minutes you
need until help arrives.
离开，也许你可以去当博士。 Dolittle路线，如果您跑步，请与它成为朋友
Number nine.
尽可能快地走开，或者应该摔倒在地并玩死
A Faulty Parachute.
熊正在做出您的决定[音乐]
Now, you decide to do a group skydive to
站稳脚跟可能会与黑熊一起工作，因为它们的数量要少得多
celebrate not drowning, because why not?
领土或侵略性，但棕熊不会退缩到小人类
As you leap from the plane,
像你逃跑或与熊成为朋友不是明智的举动，无论
you feel like you're truly flying
棕熊攻击类型，唯一的选择是用
and you're more alive than ever.
抓住膝盖到下巴，双手抓住脖子
Not for long, though.
你不是威胁，它会消失，希望它能致命地杀死7号致命毒液
Your bad luck continues and
your parachute doesn't open.
您的动物问题远未结束，而另一件事
You're plummeting from the
sky at an alarming rate.
漫步时，被毒蛇咬伤，小腿上咬伤，
And as you spin out of control,
周围没有人可以帮助您做什么使自己摆脱困境
you see the hard ground
below rushing up at you.
这个烂摊子你可以尝试吸毒，如果
How are you going to get
out of this predicament?
您足够灵活，或者最好静坐并应用
Are you going to curl into
a ball to protect your
止血带扎到被咬的腿上，也许用干净的方法洗咬
head and your internal
organs from the impact?
水和绷带可以帮助您避免某些死亡
Will you put your faith
in the reserve parachute?
快想想，如果您找不到阻止它的方法，毒液将会杀死您
Or will you try and maneuver to
如果您一直在练习瑜伽并且正在练习瑜伽，那么第一个选择可能就是吸引人
another skydiver and cling onto them?
超级弯曲，但是当它可能渗入时，您真的要在嘴里放毒吗
Be quick.
你的细小伤口和牙龈的血流我不这么认为
You only have 10 seconds until
洗伤口是不好的，也不会阻止已经存在的毒液
it's too late to save yourself.
在你内心的唯一选择就是静坐并保持镇静以止血
(drum beats)
抽水并用止血带阻止毒液进入
The answer to your problem is clear.
身体的其余部分第六个邪恶教授的谜题
The reserve parachute is the only
当您发现动物时，动物并不是您生命的唯一威胁
thing guaranteed to save your life.
幸运的是，邪恶教授抓住了教授的感觉，并给予了
Curling up into a ball
might minimize damage,
你有机会获得自由，别搞砸了，他给了你三扇门
but it also might not.
选择以导致自由，但另一种导致死亡，你只能
And as for clinging to another skydiver,
在做出选择之前先问一个是或否的问题，邪恶的教授会回答
you'll get them killed too.
老实说，如果您指向一个自由之门，那么这个问题，但如果您指向一个自由之门，可能会说谎
Number eight.
到死亡之门，你要问的问题是什么，你最好快点决定
Paws of Death.
邪恶教授以其耐心而闻名
Back on land, you're out for a
stroll in the great outdoors.
您唯一的希望是门a的位置，问门B是否导致自由
It's a beautiful, sunny day
他说是，请选择B门，如果答案是否定的，请选择C门。
and you're whistling as you walk.
该图向您展示了我的解决方案的工作原理
You're daydreaming about
what you'll have for
五号大自然的报仇是的，你让自己陷入了更多麻烦
lunch once you get back to your campsite.
但这一次是你的悠闲时光
So much, though, that you
don't notice the huge,
大概开车避免在致命的麻烦之后漫步
brown bear standing a few
meters in front of you.
动物，您已经停下来在田野旁放松自己
A wave of panic washes over you as the
就在这条路，天气变得阴暗而暴风雨，龙卷风降落
bear looks into your eyes and growls.
可怕地靠近你，没有庇护所，你要如何摆脱这个困境
What will you do to
escape the paws of death?
纠结也许你可以爬上一棵树，在绿树成荫的树枝下躲避
Should you stand your ground
and try to scare it off?
您应该在田野中找到沟渠并在其中or缩还是要破折号
Maybe you can go the Doctor
Dolittle route and befriend it.
为你的车，希望你能在龙卷风之前就到达
Should you run away as fast as you can?
快点，你有十秒钟，直到它扫清你
Or should you drop to
the ground and play dead?
[音乐]
The bear's approaching.
爬树对你没有多大好处，你打算如何挂在树上
Make your decision.
龙卷风打到它为你的车跑是冒险的，即使你做到了
(drum beats)
龙卷风仍然可以抓住您并接载车辆以及所有最佳选择
Standing your ground might
work with a black bear,
是要进入沟渠，如果
as they're much less
territorial or aggressive.
龙卷风经过你，它可能无法将你从躲藏处抬起
But a brown bear won't back
down to a tiny human like you.
老实说，虽然这对你有帮助，但她却让自己留在外面
Running away or befriending a bear
第一名4恐怖隧道这是一个安静的周末，所以您决定
isn't a wise move, no matter the type.
去当地的山洞里探寻一个运气和你一样多的人
With a brown bear attack, your only option
不应该那样做，但无论如何都要离开，让惊喜惊奇最糟糕的事情
is to drop to the ground
with your knees to
可以想象的是，您设法找到的出口区块发生了滑坡
your chin and your hands
protecting your neck.
替代隧道，但很方便，它们都有路标告诉您
When it sees you're not a
threat, it will walk away.
危险潜伏在其中，您将不得不从包含以下内容的隧道中进行选择
Hopefully.
熔化的熔岩将使您活着，而另一个巨大的滑坡将掩埋
Number seven.
您杀死所有动物或数千只致命蜘蛛的有毒气体
Deadly Venom.
您将选择哪个路线做出决定洞穴现在可能会崩溃
Sadly, your animal
troubles are far from over,
其中的三个隧道肯定会杀死人类，但其中一个
and on another one of
your eventful strolls,
只要您实际上是一个人，它们只会对动物构成危险
you get bitten by a venomous snake.
选择您可以不受伤害地逃脱的充气隧道
The bite is on your lower leg,
三号红色和蓝色药丸想象这是您盲目生病，您有
and there's nobody around to help.
周围没有人可以帮助你穷人才能生存，你必须服用两片
What are you going to do to
get yourself out of this mess?
每一天，蓝色和红色的药丸都会闻到味道和味道
You could try to suck the venom
完全一样，所以无法知道医生总是把哪个
out if you're flexible enough.
药丸放在您每天的药盒中，但有一天您将药盒滑落
Or, maybe it would be better to sit still
混合了这两天哦，不，你今天需要吃药，
and apply a tourniquet to the bitten leg.
直到明天医生才能找你，你将如何确定
Perhaps washing the bite
with clean water and applying
您应该服用的四滴药[音乐]
a bandage will help you
avoid certain death.
唯一的方法是将所有四个药丸都切成两半，然后放一半
Think fast.
每个都分成两个单独的堆，最后您将有两个堆
The venom will kill you if
四半保证您服用正确的剂量第二致命
you don't find a way to stop it.
地狱哦，不，你被困在另一个房间里，这次着火了怎么办
(drum beats)
在这种情况下，您和您之间的火焰正在燃烧
The first option might
be tempting if you've
门，没有其他逃脱地狱的方法
been practicing yoga and are super bendy.
消防员正在赶路，但您需要弄清楚如何保持安全
But do you really want venom in your
直到他们到来，​​您才考虑您的选择
mouth when it could seep into your
您可以站在地面上并保持尽可能低的高度，也可以站在
bloodstream from tiny cuts in your gums?
椅子靠近天花板，您可以脱下衣服以保持凉爽
I don't think so.
可能会让消防员感到恐惧，或者您可以躲在桌子底下
Washing your wound is no good either.
你会戒烟的那一刻烟越来越浓
It won't stop the venom
that's already inside you.
[音乐]
Your only option is to sit still
首先坐在椅子上是一个糟糕的主意
and keep calm to stop your blood pumping
烟雾和热量都上升，所以您不会有机会带走您的
and to apply a tourniquet
to block the venom
脱掉衣服会使皮肤暴露在高温下，这不是您想要的
from getting into the rest of your body.
精致的零件和放在办公桌下面并不能真正帮助您
Number six.
唯一的选择是降低地板的高度，以免使您窒息
Professor Evil's Puzzle.
从烟雾中等待，直到帮助来临
Animals aren't the only
threat to your life,
恐惧房间的第一名恭喜您，您已经做到了
as you find out when you're
captured by Professor Evil.
最后的难题，您因为罪行太可怕而被判死刑
Luckily, the professor's feeling generous,
的，你很残酷，不寻常的execution子手给你选择
and gives you one opportunity to get free.
四个坦克，您将从顶部进入并满足命运
Don't mess it up.
第一个房间的增值税额和您的胸部一样深
He gives you three doors to choose from.
第二个是充满嗜血的凶手准备杀死第三个是
Two lead to freedom, but
the other leads to death.
熊熊烈火熊熊燃烧，第四个有一个充满嗜血的水池
And you can only ask one yes-or-no
六个月内没有吃掉的鲨鱼，您会选择令人恐惧的命运
question before making your choice.
[音乐]
Professor Evil will answer the question
每个房间听起来都令人难以置信，但如果我是你，我会去
honestly if you point to a freedom door,
如果鲨鱼已经六个月没有进食了，那么到处都是鲨鱼出没的水域
but might lie if you
point to the death door.
他们都死了，对你没有任何危险，恭喜你幸免于难
What's your question going to be?
您解决了10个致命的谜语吗？
You'd better decide quickly.
在下面，感谢您的观看[音乐]
Professor Evil isn't
known for his patience.